

Hello!

My name is Fredrika Trygg. I'm a 24 year old girl from Malmö. I am an outgoing and curious girl who aims to develop and always wants to learn more. Qualities I am described to have and that I value highly are humility towards others, inclusivity, and an flexibility to work both with different people in teams as much as I work and focus alone. I am an E-commerce Manager graduated at IHM Business School in Malmö.

Education

- E-commerce Manager, IHM Business School, Aug 2022-2024
- Courses in pedagogy, Malmö University, Sep 2020 Sep 2021
- Food sustainability, Folkuniversitetet, Sep 2021-May 2022
- **High School Diploma**, Aesthetic Program with a Music Focus Malmö Latin School, 2016 2019

Experience

- Sales and marketing coordinator ImmuneBiotech. Aug 2024-present. I independently manage practical tasks related to the company's webshop, including handling customer shipments, logistics, inventory, and customer communication via email. I also manage digital marketing tasks, such as developing the company's webshop, conducting follow-up/analysis, managing email campaigns, writing copy and creating content, handling GutMagnific's social media accounts, and advertising on different platforms. My role also includes professionally communicating with customers via email and phone in both Swedish and English.
- Marketing Intern Venture Cup. January 2024 May 2024. Responsible for creating content and materials for Instagram, TikTok, LinkedIn, and Facebook.
 I write press releases for our website in Wordpress. I also have knowledge for the type of content published and tailored to different platforms based on the target audience. I created newsletter in our CRM-solution. I managed our

TikTok account, creating content that resonates with the target audience. I creatively brainstormed new ideas for content and stay updated on the latest trends in the social media world to drive engagement and views for growth.

- Sales Associate BikBok. August 2023 Feb 2024. Helping customers during their shopping journey. Working in the cash register. Visual merchandiser.
- **Consultant** Manpower. March 2022 September 2023: Loading and packing packages for further shipment, etc.
- Podcast Host, Content Creator Malmö UN Association. July 2021 2024
 Planning and recording podcasts with Malmö UN Association, focusing on the Global Goals. The podcast is called "Globala målen podden."
- Childcare Assistant, Malmö Stad. September 2020 May 2022: Taking care of children, ensuring their well-being, at various preschools in Malmö, Södertull.
- Warehouse Worker Filial af Danmark AB. July September 2020: Packed face masks and fertility products for delivery to customers.
- Sales Associate ZARA. August 2019 May 2020: Assisted customers in finding the right clothing, operated the cash register, tidied up the store, and restocked items in the warehouse.
- Service Assistant SUS Malmö. June August 2018 and June-August 2019: Assisted doctors, nurses, and nursing assistants in the orthopedic department.
- Restaurant Worker Café Smyge and Magazinet. April 2017 September 2017: Prepared food, served guests, cleaned, and operated the cash register.
- **Healthcare Assistant** Home Care Services Svedala. June 2016 August 2016: Mostly worked alongside nursing assistants to support them in caring for the elderly.

Language:

Svenska - Modersmål Engelska – Flytande Norska- Mellan Danska – Mellan